Jerry Davis

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jerry-davis-8991641b4/ **Email:** Jwdavis8589@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://www.silverwindworkshop.com/

SUMMARY

Game Designer with successfully shipped Game Design commercial product for the popular Dungeons & Dragons virtual tabletop, Roll20. Award-winning Software Engineer with over 2 years of experience working with a large codebase for BlueShield of California servicing 4.5 million customers and over 65,000 physicians.

EXPERIENCE

Independent Game Designer Silverwind Workshop

February 2022 – Current

- Independent game design focused on systems design for Dungeons & Dragons 5th Edition via Roll20 Marketplace.
- "The customization of this system has honestly made it hard for me to go back to standard D&D. It honestly impresses me
 the depth and creativity that is present in this. If more flair and flexibility in combat is what you want, this is for you."
 -User Review for Skills Trees & Leveling Overhaul
- Free demo materials available in portfolio website.
- Drove 100% of game design, user experience, and graphical design.

Senior Associate Developer

Infosys

March 2021 - March 2023

- 100% experience working for BlueShield of California client as a Software Engineer contractor.
- Reduced web application overhead for 50% of pages.
- Developed, bug-fixed, and performed code analysis of codebase used by 1 in 9 Californians.
- Led team of 5 agile software engineers while providing Knowledge Transfers for Portal Support Team, Urgent Solutions Team, and Junior Associates.

Software Engineer

Revature

November 2020 - March 2021

- Developed reactive one-page web applications in React and RESTful APIs in Java Springboot.
- Drove development for several teams as both Scrum Master and Lead Developer.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Computer Science

Arkansas State University

August 2016 – May 2020

Graduated with Cum Laude.

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

- Cobalt Cloud Certification Infosys
- Global Agile Developer Certification Infosys
- Infosys Certificate of Appreciate Going the Extra Mile
- Infosys Certificate of Excellence Rising Star

SKILLS

- Unreal Engine, Unity, Gamemaker Studio
- Systems Design, Tabletop Game Design
- C#, C++, JavaScript
- Scripting (Python & Lua)
- Mathematics, Problem Solving, Debugging, Communication
- Git, Jira, Trello, Agile, Scrum Methodology